Rohan Badala

Delhi, Delhi

badalarohan3639_u9c@indeedemail.com

8010938656

Rohan Badala, a graduate in Computer Science & engineering, is currently working as a SAP-ISU consultant in BSES

Yamuna Power Limited (A joint venture of Reliance Infra & Govt. of NCT Delhi).

He has a total of 8.5 years of experience with 3 years of experience as a software developer & 5.5 years of

experience in ERP SAP-ISU Billing and Invoicing in regulated and de-regulated market of electricity distribution. He

has exposure in Project wise analysis, Branch wise analysis in SAP-ISU.

Work Experience

Sr. Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited September 2020 to Present

Implementation of GNM & VNM Billing.

RESPONSIBILITIES

Communicating with the business people to understand the business requirements.

Writing functional specification as per business requirements.

Billing master Data configuration (Operand, Schema, Rate structure, etc).

Understanding Functionality of Tariff Design (Billing Schema, Rate determination, Rate).

Guiding users during the User Acceptance tests.

Analyzing the Batch Job issues related to billing and invoicing.

Performing Integrated testing (Inter Module) & training for End user.

Sr. Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited August 2020 to November 2020

Implementation of TCS (Tax collected at source).

Sr. Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited July 2019 to December 2019

Implementation of CCTV Billing & STREET LIGHT Billing.

Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited April 2018 to February 2019

Open Access project (EDM & RTP BILLING)

Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited - Delhi, Delhi August 2017 to February 2018

Complete process Changes / Implementations as per new Supply Code-2017 as per DERC, Delhi Govt. order.

Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited July 2016 to May 2017

Implementation of Data Archiving of SAP-ISU. GST implementation IN SAP-ISU.

Asst. Manager

BSES Yamuna Power Limited July 2013 to June 2016

DTM (Distribution transformer tracking module) -

An ASP.NET web based application to track all the 47 DT activities of O&M, MMG, Business, Enforcement & Surveillance departments.

IOMS (Intelligent outage management system) -

A system to manage all the customer related complaints, power outage & grid network over GIS system.

Education

B.E. in Computer Science

College of technology & engineering June 2008 to June 2012

C.B.S.E in Board

St. Gregorios Sr. Sec. School - Udaipur, Rajasthan June 2000 to June 2007

Skills / IT Skills

- SAP-ISU: Basic understanding of business processes in IS-Utilities.
 Billing / Invoicing: Worked on several defects related to Billing / Invoicing etc.
 ABAP: Basic knowledge of ABAP debugging and tables.
 ASP.NET, Javascript & Oracle.
- SAP ISU BILLING
- SAP ISU BILLING AND INVOICING